cybrosys.com 2019-07-09

# Privacy Policies - Cybrosys Technologies

### Important Information That You Should Read

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Cybrosys Technologies collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users while they visit the website www.cybrosys.com, reach out Cybrosys through email, fill data in a contact document or else, or while they apply for jobs displayed in Cybrosys website. This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Cybrosys Technologies.

Cybrosys have created this Privacy Policy, to summarize our online data protection guidelines and briefly describes why or which data regarding users (you) will be gathered by Cybrosys.The policy also explains how the data concerning you shall be utilized, how you, as a data subject, will handle your personal information and how to contact us whenever you require. This Policy also describes our use of cookies.

Kindly read this Policy with care prior to browsing this ‘website’. We use or process your information only according to the explanations in this Policy. Our ‘websites’ are not intended for kids below the 16 years of age, and we will not consciously gather personal information from kids within this age limit.

The Policy is a fundamental element of the Terms of Use of this ‘website’. In future Cybrosys may update the Policy, therefore kindly ensure to go through this policy on a timely manner.

Kindly reach us at info@cybrosys.com whenever you want to share your doubts or comments with regards to the policy.

### What Cybrosys Does With Your Information?

Considering the ‘GDPR’ or EU General Data Protection Regulation, Cybrosys is a processor and controller of the personal information given via this ‘website’ and gathered in other means. Here ‘controller’ implies that we are accountable to decide how we use and hold personal data connected to you.

Cybrosys utilizes the third-party ‘workable’ for recruitment work processes. Through the submission of an online application for vacancies displayed in the ‘website’ you deliberately offer your resume, personal data and contact data, and any other data you wish, and consent that the data shall be gathered and processed by either ‘workable’ or ‘Cybrosys’. In similar instances Cybrosys maintains that the information controller and workable will be the processor of your information. We use tools like Twak to, Google Analytics, Website Contact Form, Google Tag Manager for monitoring and collecting the user information.

However, the company shall collect personal identification information from users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain site related activities.

### Which Information Regarding You Do We Gather?

. 

We only gather data regarding you that is essential for us to help you to utilize tour Website or reach us, and no more than to the level purposely offered in the ‘policy’.

###### Data we get from you

When you contact us via email or via the contact form, you provide us your name, phone number, e-mail address, communication content and data associated with the communication.

### Why Do We Process Your Personal Data?

Only when Cybrosys possesses a legal basis to process your personal information, we will do so. The legal basis depends on the conditions we have gathered and require to utilize your personal information for. Cybrosys will process your personal information since:

  * You gave us the consent to use your personal data
  * We have to comply with some legal obligation
  * Comes under our rightful business well-being

More particularly, personal information offered to us via this website and personal information we gathered from you or third parties or from public resources shall be utilized for any purpose according to the legal It grounds.

### Each Company That Reach European Citizens Must Comply With GDPR

On the 25th of May 2018, the GDPR or General Data Protection Regulation, Regulation (EU) 2016/679, was placed into action in each of the twenty-eight nations in Europe. The GDPR is a fresh rule agreed by the European Union that wants to enhance transparency and the efficiency of information protection activities. It affects how companies must describe and get consent for fresh and current prospects from users that subscribe to their email lists and data about the users are saved inside the CRM and other processes.

Apart from the EU members, you must understand that that any business which markets products or services to EU citizens, not considering its location, is subject to this regulation. By complying with GDPR needs, companies will avoid paying expensive penalties when enhancing customer information protection and trust.

After this privacy rule has been active, websites which shall not comply will be unreachable to European nations. Many famous websites were temporarily blocked such as the Chicago Tribune and LA Times. If your company website gathers any of the regulated information from European citizens — that company is legally responsible to comply with GDPR.
